{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"1135","question":"\u0d10\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c "},{"q_number":"1136","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1137","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d [ \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ] \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b \u0d0e \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1138","question":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e \u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1139","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1964"},{"q_number":"1140","question":"\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f.1789 \r\n"},{"q_number":"1141","question":"\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d41\u0d15\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c "},{"q_number":"1142","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e \u0d35\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d7c ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"1143","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 "},{"q_number":"1144","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4a\u0d38\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1145","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d "},{"q_number":"1146","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d"},{"q_number":"1147","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d17\u0d57\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e "},{"q_number":"1148","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d30 "},{"q_number":"1149","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"1960"},{"q_number":"1150","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24-\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d39\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2e"},{"q_number":"1151","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1152","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1153","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d39"},{"q_number":"1154","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"1996 \u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d 17"},{"q_number":"1155","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1854"},{"q_number":"1156","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d31 \u0d09\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d34\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1157","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d12\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1158","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1159","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e"},{"q_number":"1160","question":"\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d27\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1161","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1162","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1163","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ,\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1164","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1165","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d24\u0d46\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f ?","answer":"60"},{"q_number":"1166","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1167","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d2e \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1489"},{"q_number":"1168","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"1169","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1170","question":"\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d33\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1725"},{"q_number":"1171","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"2005 \u0d0f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d 1"},{"q_number":"1172","question":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d37\u0d15\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1173","question":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1174","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d33\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1175","question":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 644 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1176","question":"\u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1177","question":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d33\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1178","question":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1179","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1180","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1181","question":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1182","question":"\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1183","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1184","question":"2011\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1185","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1186","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7d\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d57\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1187","question":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d34\u0d41\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1188","question":"\u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1189","question":"\u0d26\u0d48\u0d35\u0d26\u0d36\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41"},{"q_number":"1190","question":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1191","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1192","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1193","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41-\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1194","question":"\u0d38\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1195","question":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1196","question":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d32\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1708"},{"q_number":"1197","question":"\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1198","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1199","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1200","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d7b red \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1019"},{"q_number":"1201","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1202","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1203","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d (1899)"},{"q_number":"1204","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1205","question":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1206","question":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1207","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1208","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1209","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1210","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41"},{"q_number":"1211","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1961"},{"q_number":"1212","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1213","question":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1214","question":"\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1215","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1216","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1217","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02\u0d35\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1218","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d7d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1219","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1220","question":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e"},{"q_number":"1221","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30"},{"q_number":"1222","question":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4b \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1223","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1224","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1225","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1226","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f"},{"q_number":"1227","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1228","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d40\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a"},{"q_number":"1229","question":". \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e"},{"q_number":"1230","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30"},{"q_number":"1231","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1232","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1233","question":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d1f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1234","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1235","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d28\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1236","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1237","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1238","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1239","question":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d28\u0d02: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1240","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d35\u0d31 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1241","question":"\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1242","question":". \u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1243","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1244","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1245","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1246","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d43\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1247","question":"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1248","question":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d48\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1249","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f: ","answer":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1250","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1251","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1252","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1253","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d1f"},{"q_number":"1254","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1255","question":". \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1256","question":". \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1257","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02: ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d(\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d)"},{"q_number":"1258","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1259","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d (\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d)"},{"q_number":"1260","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d(\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32)"},{"q_number":"1261","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1262","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d."},{"q_number":"1263","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1264","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1265","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1266","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ","answer":"\u0d0f\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d32"},{"q_number":"1267","question":". \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1268","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1269","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a"},{"q_number":"1270","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ","answer":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f(\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f)"},{"q_number":"1271","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1272","question":". \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d05\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32"},{"q_number":"1273","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?","answer":" \u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a"},{"q_number":"1274","question":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32"},{"q_number":"1275","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d1f\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1276","question":". \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d32\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f"},{"q_number":"1277","question":". \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1278","question":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1279","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d32\u0d35\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1280","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d? ","answer":"1989 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d 25"},{"q_number":"1281","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1282","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"1283","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02: ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1284","question":"\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1285","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02: ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1286","question":". \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1287","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1288","question":". \u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"1990 \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f 4"},{"q_number":"1289","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02: ","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1290","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d? ","answer":"1930"},{"q_number":"1291","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1292","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d30\u0d35\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1293","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1294","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1295","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d37\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1296","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1297","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1298","question":". \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1299","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1300","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d (\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d)"},{"q_number":"1301","question":". \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1302","question":". \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d15\u0d32: ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1303","question":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1304","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1305","question":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02: ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1306","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1307","question":". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05","answer":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1308","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1309","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1310","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"}]},"code":"100"}